

YURIY GRISHCHENKO

Full-Stack Developer (MERN)

DETAILS

Contact
Minsk, Belarus
grishchenko-yuriy1996@yandex.by
+375293174095

Date of birth 12.11.1996

PROFILE

I am a full-stack developer (MERN). I have extensive commercial experience as a front-end developer and experience in writing back-end parts for my own projects. I have a strong knowledge in JS.

I was a temporary team leader when ours went on vacation. I have experience in code review. Responsible approach to the development process. I delve into the essence of projects and offer my ideas for implementation

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend developer, Brimit, Minsk

APRIL 2022 - PRESENT

Was a developer on projects based on various CMS systems. Studied and used Typescript, Nx, Zustand, styled components, Material UI v5, PWA studio etc. Worked in an English speaking team.

Frontend developer, Freelance, Minsk

NOVEMBER 2020 - MARCH 2021

Developed the front-end part of the payment system based on metronic

Frontend developer, Scrump, Minsk

AUGUST 2020 - APRIL 2022

Worked in the blockchain ecosystem mineplex. Studied React, Next js, Redux, Material UI v4, Formik + yup. I was a temporary team leader when ours went on vacation. Did a code review.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Electronics Engineer-Programmer, Belarusian state university of informatics and radioelectronics, Minsk

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2018

Master of technical sciences, Belarusian state university of informatics and radioelectronics, Minsk SEPTEMBER 2018 – JUNE 2020

LINKS

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u> <u>Telegram</u>

HTML5 + CSS3 / SCSS	JavaScript
Typescript	React
Git	MongoDB
Express js	Node.js
Redux	Material UI
Styled-components	nx.dev
HOBBIES I love going to the gym and I do it regularly. I also constantly learn something new and practice it.	
Trove going to the gynrand rad it regularly. Falso constantly learn something new and practice it.	
LANGUAGES	
Russian	English

SKILLS